Icon: 1024*1024
banner: 1024*500
Screen shoot: 1242*2208
Screen shoot: 2048*2732

Jumping Jumping Description 

Bạn sẽ làm gì nếu phát hiện một kho báu đang nằm sâu trong rừng ở một hang động (cave) đầy chướng ngại vật nguy hiểm? Cùng theo chân người thợ mỏ (miner) vào trong hang để giúp anh vượt qua khó khăn khai thác số vàng & kim cương. Hãy cẩn thận những chú dơi và tảng đá, bất kỳ lúc nào cũng có thể rơi hoặc lăn trúng người thợ mỏ

What you gonna do if you happen to know about a treasure deep in the forest, but the cave is full of dangerous traps? Let’s accompany the brave miner and help him defeat all the challenges to collect as much gold and diamond as possible. However, watch out for the bats and the rocks that can attack you out of nowhere. 
★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★ 
Có thể chọn 1 trong 2 chế độ di chuyển: Vuốt hoặc Chạm,  để điều khiển nhân vật qua trái, phải, lên, xuống  vượt các chướng ngại vật để thu thập các Item.
Có 2 mức độ: Dễ (điểu khiển 1 nhân vật), và Khó (điều khiển cùng lúc 2 nhân vật)
Càng nhiều item, điểm càng cao
Có thể thay đổi nhân vật mà bạn muốn

You can either Swap or Touch to move the miner up, down, to the right or to the left to collect the items.
There are 2 play modes: Easy (control 1 character) and Hard (control 2 characters at the same time)
The more items you collect, the more points you get.
You can change the character if you want.
★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★ 
Jumping Jumping is a registered trademark of Starseed
Follow us: http://topit.vietnamworks.com/companies/company/STARSEED/
We appreciate all your comments about the Game. Please send to: contact@starseed.fr to get the best support.

Jumping Jumping Keywords
jump,dash,gold,cave,miner,swipe,race,geometry,impossible,endless,hard,difficulty,mini,offline,ping

